<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on ⌨️🤷🏻‍♂️📷</title>
    <link>https://andysalerno.com/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on ⌨️🤷🏻‍♂️📷</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 13 Jun 2021 09:44:14 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://andysalerno.com/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Bear plus snowflake equals polar bear</title>
      <link>https://andysalerno.com/posts/weird-emojis/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Jun 2021 09:44:14 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andysalerno.com/posts/weird-emojis/</guid>
      <description>Prelude: e and e Quick, how many bytes make up the following line? No tricks, I promise.
Hello! The correct answer is: 6. Or 7, if you want to be pedantic and include the newline, but let&amp;rsquo;s not.
This is simple enough; this page is encoded as UTF-8, which implies 8-bits per ASCII character, or a byte per character.
Let&amp;rsquo;s play again. How many bytes make up the following line?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>📷 First time out with the XPro 3</title>
      <link>https://andysalerno.com/posts/xpro3-first-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 May 2021 21:57:56 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andysalerno.com/posts/xpro3-first-day/</guid>
      <description>After a few years of shooting with the X-T20, I&amp;rsquo;ve swapped up to the X-Pro3.
For my first outing with this camera, of course I chose Pike Place Market. It&amp;rsquo;s surely the easiest place in Seattle to be a street photographer. People are comfortable, having fun, and cameras are everywhere.
  Click to view  I haven&amp;rsquo;t shot around Pike Place Market in a long time; even before the pandemic, I&amp;rsquo;d walked up and down that market so many times that it was starting to become too familiar.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to create a Hugo-based markdown blog</title>
      <link>https://andysalerno.com/posts/another-one/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Aug 2020 15:48:23 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andysalerno.com/posts/another-one/</guid>
      <description>Step 1: The spark ignites Oooh, look at this cool person&amp;rsquo;s blog post that was posted on Hacker News&amp;hellip; Why don&amp;rsquo;t I have cool, minimal blog like this?
Step 2: Pick your theme Spend two hours browsing minimal Hugo themes until you find one that&amp;rsquo;s simple yet functional.
Step 3: Simplify Why does this &amp;ldquo;simple&amp;rdquo; theme include google analytics, disqus, and javascript auto day/night theme detection?
I should gut it of all the stuff I don&amp;rsquo;t need&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
